mbclub.co.uk 2018-03-22

# Privacy Policy | MBClub UK - Bringing together Mercedes Enthusiasts

__

**MBClub UK - Bringing together Mercedes Enthusiasts**

[Home](http://forums.mbclub.co.uk/) [Forums](http://forums.mbclub.co.uk/) >

Privacy Policy including information on Cookies 

  * MBClub UK recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.
  * This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the MBClub UK web site.
  * By registering to MBClub UK you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Credit Card numbers are stored by us.
  * All posts and content posted to this site become the property of MBClub UK where such ownership does not conflict with existing copyrights. You also understand that posts may be deleted or modified to comply with local laws. Alternatively, not claiming ownership, but rights for use: you agree to grant MBClub UK permission for perpetual and unlimited use of all posts and other content posted to this site.
  * MBClub UK also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as MBClub UK. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)
  * Visiting our website with your browser settings adjusted to accept cookies tells us that you want to use our products and services and that you consent to our use of cookies and other technologies to provide them to you as described in this Privacy Policy.
  * MBClub UK will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant legislation.
  * All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.
  * You have a legal right for the personal information held at MBClub UK to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please contact us if you need help.
  * MBClub UK will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.
  * This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA exists on MBClub UK
  * This website will auto insert links in any posts that are created to content and this will generate revenue for mbclub.co.uk. When a link is clicked a background java script automatically analyses this action and if it's one of the merchants who are affiliated then the mbclub uk ID is appended on the end of the URL.
  * This Privacy Policy may be modified at/any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. If you have any questions regarding your privacy, then Contact Us

__

**MBClub UK - Bringing together Mercedes Enthusiasts**

[Home](http://forums.mbclub.co.uk/) [Forums](http://forums.mbclub.co.uk/) >
